http://maplecrestgolf.com/index.php/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Forbes Field Forever’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, www.maplecrestgolf.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
This policy is effective as of January 23, 2019.
Recent Posts
Hiring the Ideal Production Crew for Your Movie
What Are The Advantages of Having Concrete Floorings?
Importance of Routine Pool Maintenance
Importance of Internet Marketing for Any Kinds of Business
All About Different Movie Genres
Search for:
Recent Comments
Maplecrest GolfHiring the Ideal Production Crew for Your Movie January 15, 2020It can be an overwhelming task to hire a movie crew. You’ve got a lot of crucial positions to fill. How can you examine them? How can you ensure you hire professional ones? Where should you hire in the first place?  You have probably heard a lot of stories about hiring an unprofessional crew who ruined projects […] secure_adminWhat Are The Advantages of Having Concrete Floorings? January 15, 2020When we think about concrete floors, there are associated words to it such as “industrial”, “prison-like” or “cold.” However, with its capability to take on polished sheen and color, on top with its several pros, concrete might be your new holy grail to be used on your projects in the future. Get ready to learn […] secure_adminImportance of Routine Pool Maintenance January 15, 2020To maintain your swimming pool for it to be ready and sparkling clean for your incoming summer party, you must do a weekly cleaning on a regular basis. Your weekly pool maintenance must include checking water circulation, removing foliage and dirt, vacuuming, cleaning the skimmers, checking pH levels, inspecting the filter, and shock treatment. It is totally […] secure_adminImportance of Internet Marketing for Any Kinds of Business January 15, 2020In terms of your business’ success, internet marketing serves a major role. To promote your services and products and to market yourself, you should rely on the assistance that internet marketing has to offer. If you’re considering to begin a brand or you’re about to start and you wish to optimize your business, it is recommended for […] secure_adminAll About Different Movie Genres January 15, 2020If you want to know more about different types of existing movie genres, you will be astonished to learn that there are actually major film genres and their sub-genres. There are also known as “other categories, which nobody specifically discusses. Below is a list of the well-known and the main kinds of movie genres explained:  […] secure_admin Archives
January 2020
Categories
Concrete Company
Film
Online Marketing
Pool Cleaning
